Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) records, 1846-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean’s Files 1916-2008
  - 1969-1970
    - Committee (Box 178)
      - Curriculum
        - Communications from Student Committees or Individuals (Box 178)
        - Course Mart (Box 178)
        - Distribution Requirement (Including Language) (Box 178)
        - General and Miscellaneous (Box 178)
        - Minutes (Box 178)
        - Pass-Fail Option (Box 178)
      - Draft Regental Bylaws (Box 178)
      - Executive
        - Agendas (Box 178)
        - Minutes to be Bound (Box 178)
        - 8-27-69--Before 7/1/70, 33 folders (Box 178)
      - Human Subjects, Use of (Box 179)
      - Institutional Cooperation
        - Conference Liberal Arts Deans (Box 179)
        - Salaries, Other Universities (Box 179)
      - Joint Capital Outlay (Box 179)
      - Junior Year Abroad
        - Africa (Box 179)
      - Library (Box 179)
      - LS&A Preparatory (Box 179)
      - L.S.A.--Medical School Integrated Program (Box 179)
      - Nominating (Box 179)
      - Part B Faculty Code, Revision of (Box 179)
      - Pilot Program (Box 179)
      - Studies in Religion (Box 179)
      - Teacher Education and Certification (Box 179)
      - University Lands (Box 179)
      - Walgreen Chair (Box 179)
      - Western European Studies (Box 179)
    - Council of Colleges of Arts and Sciences (Box 179)
    - D (Box 179)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 179)
    - Dean's Office (Box 179)
    - Decision-Making (Box 179)
    - Departmental Statements (Box 179)
    - E (Box 179)
    - Education, School of (Box 179)
    - Elections (Box 179)
    - Employment of Minorities Groups (Box 179)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 179)
    - Enrollment (Box 179)
    - Extension Service (Box 179)
    - F (Box 179)
    - Faculty
      - Handbook (Box 179)
      - Letters to (Box 179)
      - Meeting
        - January (Box 179)
        - March 2, 1970 (Box 179)
      - Proposal Submitted by Student Assembly (Box 179)
    - Fleming, Robben W.--President (Box 179)
    - G (Box 179)
    - Graduate School
      - Executive Committee (Box 179)
    - H (Box 179)
    - Haber, William (Box 179)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 179)
    - Honors Council (Box 179)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Box 179)
    - Huber Commission (Box 179)
    - I (Box 180)
    - Institute
      - Public Policy Studies (Box 180)
      - Science and Technology (Box 180)
      - Social Research (Box 180)
      - Study of Mental Retardation (Box 180)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 180)
    - Inter-Office Memorandums (Box 180)
    - J (Box 180)
    - Junior Year
      - France (Box 180)
      - Freiburg (Box 180)
    - K (Box 180)
    - King Fund, Martin Luther (Box 180)
    - L (Box 180)
    - Law School (Box 180)
    - Library
      - Science, School of (Box 180)
    - LSAddenda (Box 180)
    - LS&A Program (Box 180)
    - M (Box 180)
    - Management Intercom (Box 180)
    - Materials Concerning a Hearing Requested by J. D. Halpern (Box 180)
    - Medical School (Box 180)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 180)
    - Merit Increases (Box 180)
    - Michigan Historical Collections Executive Committee (Box 180)
    - Music, School of (Box 180)
    - N (Box 180)
    - Norman, A. G.--Vice-President (Box 180)
    - O (Box 180)
    - Office Services (Box 180)
    - Orientation, Office of (Box 180)
    - Outstanding Achievement Award (Box 180)
    - P (Box 180)
    - Personnel Office (Box 180)
    - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory (Box 180)
    - Pierpont, W. K. (Box 180)
    - President, Report to (Box 180)
    - Professional Theatre Program (Box 180)
    - Promotions, 2 folders
      - Assistant Professor (Box 180)
      - Associate Professor (Box 180)
      - Letters (Box 180)
      - Professor (Box 180)
    - R (Box 180)
    - Regents Communication, 11 folders (Box 180)
    - Registration and Records (Box 180)
    - Representative Assembly, LSA (Box 180)
    - Research Administration, Office of (Box 180)
    - Residential College (Box 180)
    - Retirements (Box 180)
    - Review Procedures within the College of L.S.A. (Box 180)
    - Ross, Arthur, Vice-President for State Relations (Box 180)
    - S (Box 180)
    - SACUA (Box 181)
    - School Services, Bureau of (Box 181)
    - Shaw, James--Assistant Dean (Box 181)
    - Smith, Allan F.--Vice-President (Box 181)
    - Speech Clinic (Box 181)
    - Staff Benefits, Office of (Box 181)
    - Statistics (LSA) Credit Hours, Degrees, etc. (Box 181)
    - Student
      - Activities and Organizations (Box 181)
      - Affairs, Office of
        - Class Disruptions (Box 181)
        - Incident
          - January 29 1970 (Box 181)
          - February 18 1970 (Box 181)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 181)
      - Counseling (Box 181)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 181)
    - T (Box 181)
    - Teaching Fellows (Box 181)
    - U (Box 181)
    - University
      - Assembly, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - Professorships (Box 181)
    - V (Box 181)
    - Williams, R. L.--Administrative Dean (Box 181)
    - W, X, Y, Z (Box 181)
  - 1970-1971
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 181)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 181)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 181)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 181)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 181)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 181)
    - Computer and Communication Sciences, Department of (Box 181)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 181)
    - English, Department of (Box 181)
    - English Language Institute (Box 181)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 181)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 181)
    - Geology and Mineralogy, Department of (Box 181)
    - German, Department of (Box 182)
    - History, Department of (Box 182)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 182)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 182)
    - Linguistics, Department of (Box 182)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 182)
    - Naval Science, Department of (Box 182)
    - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 182)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 182)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 182)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 182)
    - Psychology, Department of
      - Audit Reports (Box 182)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 182)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 182)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 182)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 182)
    - Statistics, Department of (Box 182)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 182)
    - Museum
      - Anthropology (Box 182)
      - Archaeology (Box 182)
      - Art Executive Committee (Box 182)
      - Exhibits (Box 182)
      - Herbarium (Box 182)
      - Paleontology (Box 182)
      - Zoology (Box 182)
    - A (Box 182)
    - Academic Affairs
      - Advisory Council
        - Reports of R. L. Williams (Box 182)
      - Budget (Box 182)
      - Office--General (Box 182)
    - Administrative Board (Box 183)
    - Admissions
      - Office (Box 183)
      - Procedures (Box 183)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 183)
    - Afro-American Studies Center
      - AAAS (Box 183)
    - American
      - Association
        - Colleges for Teacher Education (Box 183)
        - University Professors (Box 183)
      - Council on Education (Box 183)
    - Association of American Universities (Box 183)
    - Awards (Box 183)
    - B (Box 183)
    - Bachelor in General Studies (Box 183)
    - Biological Station (Box 183)
    - Budget, 2 folders
      - 4% Savings (Box 183)
    - Buildings--General (Box 183)
    - C (Box 183)
    - Cash, W. L. (Box 183)
    - Center
      - Chinese Studies (Box 183)
      - Conflict Resolution, Research on (Box 183)
      - Continuing Education for Women (Box 183)
      - Coordination of Ancient and Modern Studies (Box 183)
      - East European and Russian Studies (Box 183)
      - Economic Development, Research on, 2 folders (Box 183)
      - Human Growth and Development (Box 184)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 184)
      - Language and Language Behavior, Research on (Box 184)
      - Learning and Teaching, Research on (Box 184)
      - Near East and North African Studies (Box 184)
      - Population Studies (Box 184)
      - Southern Asian Studies (Box 184)
      - Western European Studies (Box 184)
    - Chairmen
      - Departments--Letters to (Box 184)
      - Meetings (Box 184)
    - Chairmanship, Letters for (Box 184)
    - Coalition for the Use of Learning Skills (C.U.L.S.) (Box 184)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 184)
    - Commission to Study LS&A March 1970 (Box 184)
    - Commitments (Box 184)
    - Committee
      - Admissions (Box 184)
      - American Institutions Lectureship and Professorship (Box 184)
      - Cellular and Molecular Biology (Box 184)
      - College (General) (Box 184)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 184)
      - Curriculum
        - Course Mart (Box 184)
        - Distribution Requirements (Box 184)
        - General and Miscellaneous (Box 184)
        - Minutes (Box 184)
        - Pass/Fail Option (Box 184)
        - ROTC (Box 184)
      - Deanship Search, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - Director of Arts (Box 184)
      - Distinguished Professorship (Box 184)
      - Environmental Program (Box 184)
      - Executive
        - Retreat (Box 184)
      - Freshman Course Offerings (Box 184)
      - Human Subjects, Use of (Box 184)
      - Institutional Cooperation (Box 184)
      - Junior Year Abroad
        - Africa (Box 184)
      - Library (Box 184)
      - LS&A--Medical School Integrated Program (Box 184)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 184)
      - Pilot Program (Box 184)
      - Population Program Policy and Operating (Box 184)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 184)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 184)
      - Teacher Education and Certification (Box 184)
    - Council of Colleges of Arts and Sciences (Box 184)
    - Course Evaluation, Association for (Box 184)
    - D (Box 184)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 184)
    - Departmental Reports (Box 184)
    - E (Box 184)
    - Education, School of (Box 184)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 184)
    - Enrollment (Box 184)
    - Environmental Sciences (Box 184)
    - Extension Service (Box 185)
    - Faculty
      - Code (Box 185)
      - Letters to (Box 185)
    - Firearms (Box 185)
    - Fleming, Robben W.--President (Box 185)
    - Graduate
      - Assembly (Box 185)
      - School (Box 185)
      - Student Assistantship Program (Box 185)
    - H (Box 185)
    - Haber, William (Box 185)
    - Honors Council (Box 185)
    - Institute
      - Environmental Quality (Box 185)
      - Public Policy (Box 185)
      - Social Research (Box 185)
      - Study of Mental Retardation (Box 185)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 185)
    - Inter-Office Memorandums (Box 185)
    - Judicial System, University (Box 185)
    - Junior Year in Freiburg
      - Barcelona (Box 185)
    - K (Box 185)
    - Kennedy, R. L. (Box 185)
    - L (Box 185)
    - L & R Report on the LS&A College of the University of Michigan (Box 185)
    - Leaves of Absence--Sabbatical (Box 185)
    - Library
      - Science, School of (Box 185)
      - University (Box 185)
    - M (Box 185)
    - Macromolecular Research Center (Box 185)
    - Management Intercom (Box 185)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 185)
    - Music, School of (Box 185)
    - N (Box 185)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 185)
    - Netherlands Professorship, Visiting (Box 185)
    - Neurosciences (Box 185)
    - Norman, A. G.--Vice-President (Box 185)
    - North Central Association (Box 185)
    - O (Box 185)
    - Office Service (Box 185)
    - Orientation, Office of (Box 185)
    - P (Box 185)
    - Personnel Office (Box 185)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 185)
    - Phoenix Memorial Lab (Box 185)
    - Political Activity (Box 185)
    - Positions--Outside U of M (Box 185)
    - President, Report to (Box 185)
    - PROBE (Includes Photographic Negatives) (Box 185)
    - Promotions, 3 folders (Box 186)
      - Dean Shaw (Box 186)
    - Q, R (Box 186)
    - Regents Communications, 11 folders (Box 186)
    - Reorganization (Box 186)
    - Research Administration, Office of (Box 186)
    - Residential College, 2 folders (Box 186)
    - Resource Allocation Commission (Box 186)
    - Retirements (Box 186)
    - S (Box 186)
    - School Services, Bureau of (Box 186)
    - Senate Meeting
      - SACUA (Box 186)
    - Shaw, James--Assistant Dean (Box 186)
    - Smith, Allen F.--Vice-President for Academic Affairs (Box 186)
    - Student
      - Affairs, Office of
        - Disruptions
          - John Eustis 2-19-71 (Box 186)
          - Marc Leslie Van Der Hout (Box 186)
          - W. Quad Case (Box 186)
      - Fees and Fee Regulations (Box 186)
      - LS&A Government Council
        - Plan (Box 186)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 186)
    - T (Box 186)
    - Terms and Conditions of Appointment for Teaching Staff (Box 186)
    - V, W (Box 186)
    - Williams, R. L.--Administrative Dean (Box 186)
    - X, Y, Z
  - 1922-1971 (Miscellaneous)
    - Chronological Correspondence File
      - 1948-1949 (Box 187)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 187)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 187)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 187)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 187)
      - July-December 1967 (Box 187)
      - January-June 1968 (Box 188)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 188)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 188)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 188)
    - Faculty Code, 4 folders (Box 188)
    - Residential College Planning Material, 9 folders (Box 189)
    - Engineering Research Institute (Council)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 189)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 189)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 189)
      - 1956-1957 (Contracts and 1922-1971 (Miscellaneous)) (Box 189)
      - 1953-1956 (Minutes and Policy Correspondence) (Box 189)
    - Curriculum Committee
      - 1944-1945, 3 folders (Box 190)
      - December 1944-July 1955 (Box 190)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 190)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 190)
      - 1947-1948, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - 1948-1949, 3 folders (Box 190)
      - July 1948-December 1950 (Box 190)
      - 1949-1950, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - 1950 Dept. of Speech (Box 190)
      - 1950-1951, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - 1951-1952, 3 folders (Box 190)
      - October 1952-December, 1952 (Box 190)
      - 1952 Dept. of Anthropology (Box 190)
      - 1952 (Box 190)
      - 1952-1953, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - 1953 Professor Marshall M. Knappen (Box 190)
      - 1953-1954, 4 folders (Box 191)
      - 1954-1955, 2 folders (Box 191)
      - October 1954-May, 1962 (Box 191)
      - 1955-1956, 2 folders (Box 191)
      - 1955-1957 (Box 191)
      - August 1955-October, 1958 (Box 191)
      - 1955-1959 (Box 191)
      - 1955-1960 (Box 191)
      - Fall 1955-January, 1962 (Box 191)
      - 1956-1957, 4 folders (Box 192)
      - 1957 Humanities Study Comm. (Box 192)
      - 1957-1958, 4 folders (Box 192)
      - 1958-1959, 2 folders (Box 192)
      - 1958-1961 (Box 192)
      - 1959-1960, 2 folders (Box 192)
      - 1960-1961, 4 folders (Box 192)
      - 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 193)
      - October 1960-May, 1963 (Box 193)
      - 1961-1962, 5 folders (Box 193)
      - 1962-1963, 2 folders (Box 193)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 193)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 193)
      - December 1970-May, 1972 (Box 193)
      - October 1971-June, 1972 (Box 193)
    - Executive Committee (Box 194)
      - Agenda Books 1960-1962
    - Executive Committee
      - Agenda Books 1962-1963 (Box 195)
    - Statistics 1963-1964, 3 volumes (Box 195)
    - Statistics 1965-1966 (Box 195)
    - Administrative Board 1964-1965 (Box 196)
    - Advanced Placement 1956-1957 (Box 196)
    - American Culture Program 1954-1955 (Box 196)
    - Announcement (LS&A) 11/24/1958 (Box 196)
    - Biological Sciences 1959 (Box 196)
    - Blueprints for L.S.A. Buildings (Box 196)
    - Budget Request, Preliminary
      - 1955-1956 (Box 196)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 196)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 196)
    - Building
      - Addition to Angell Hall 1948-1949 (Box 196)
      - Current Space Use 1946-1947 (Box 196)
      - Needs
        - 1939-1943 (Box 196)
        - 1943-1944 (Box 196)
        - 1947-1950 (Box 196)
        - 1947-1951 (Box 196)
      - Rehabilitation and Special Equipments 1962-1963 (Box 196)
    - Center for Learning and Teaching, Ford Proposal 10/11/1965 (Box 196)
    - Chairmanship
      - Anthropology 1964 (Box 196)
      - Botany 1962 (Box 196)
      - Dept. Statements re: (Box 196)
      - Economics 1963 (Box 196)
      - English 1962 (Box 196)
      - Far East November 1963 (Box 196)
      - Geography 1964 (Box 196)
      - Journalism 1963 (Box 196)
      - Library Science 1963 (Box 196)
      - Philosophy 1962 (Box 196)
      - Political Science 1963 (Box 196)
      - Romance Language 1964 (Box 196)
      - Sociology 1963 (Box 196)
    - Chairmen
      - Department Letters 1961-1964 (Box 196)
      - Letters (Misc.) 1963-1964 (Box 196)
    - Class of 1917
      - 1956-1957 (Box 196)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 196)
    - Committee
      - Academic Affairs 1963 (Box 196)
      - Admissions 12/1965
        - Faculty Meeting 10/63 (Box 196)
      - Area Studies November, 1962 (Box 196)
      - Asia 1958-1959 (Box 196)
      - Asian Study 1956-1959 (Box 196)
    - Committee
      - Calendar 1958-1959 (Box 196)
      - Cellular Biology (Box 196)
      - Curriculum 1963 (Box 196)
      - Great Books 1954-1958 (Box 196)
      - Institute for Social Research 1958-1959 (Box 196)
      - Language and Language Behavior Study, Report of 1965 (Box 196)
      - Master List 1967-1968 (Box 196)
      - Natural Science Study
        - 1957-1958, 2 folders (Box 197)
        - 1956-1959 (Box 197)
        - Descriptions of Science Courses (Box 197)
        - Meteorology and Civil Engineering 1956 (Box 197)
        - Reports 1955 (Box 197)
        - Senior Questionnaires 1955-1956 (Box 197)
      - Social Science Study
        - 1958-1959 (Box 197)
        - Memoranda 1955-1956 (Box 197)
        - Reports 1956-1957 (Box 197)
      - Sponsored Research 1958-1959 (Box 197)
      - Unified Science Program 1957-1958 (Box 197)
      - Utilization of Faculty 1958-1958 (Box 197)
    - Concentration Programs 1958-1959 (Box 197)
    - Counseling Services 1956-1957 (Box 197)
    - Deanship 1949-1950 (Box 197)
    - Dearborn Center 1957 (Box 197)
    - Departmental Organization 1951-1952 (Box 197)
    - Education Bill 1963 (Box 197)
    - Enrollment Data 1963 (Box 197)
    - Examination Procedures 1957 (Box 197)
    - Faculty Directory Material
      - 1963-1964 (Box 197)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 197)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 197)
    - Fine Arts, Department of 1941-1942 (Box 197)
    - Fourth Semester Requirement (Box 197)
    - French Experiment 1955-1956 (Box 197)
    - Freshman Composition (Box 197)
    - General Education Programs 1953-1954 (Box 197)
    - Honors Council
      - 1955, 1958 (Box 197)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 197)
      - Executive Committee 1957-1958
        - Minutes (Box 197)
      - Faculty Meeting 10/1963 (Box 197)
      - Literature 1955-1956 (Box 197)
      - Minutes 1957-1958 (Box 197)
    - Humanities February, 1956 (Box 197)
    - Internships in General Education 1956-1957 (Box 197)
    - Jones, K. L. (Box 197)
    - Letter to the Faculty about Growth of College 1963 (Box 197)
    - Literary College Conferences (Box 198)
      - Progress Report 1950-1951 (Box 198)
      - Fall Semester 1951-1952 (Box 198)
      - Spring Semester 1952 (Box 198)
    - LS&A Statistics, Service Teaching 1962-1963 (Box 198)
    - Mathematical Building 1961-1962 (Box 198)
    - Memos 1958-1960 (Box 198)
    - Merit Increase
      - Letter 1961, 1963 (Box 198)
      - Recommendations for 1961-1962 Letters from Departments (Box 198)
    - Needs of the College of Literature, Science, and the Arts 1945-1946 (Box 198)
    - Population Studies Center Annual Report 1964-1965 (Box 198)
    - Pre-Medical Programs 1957 (Box 198)
    - Promotions
      - Letter 1963-1964 (Box 198)
      - Recommendations for 1961-1962 (Box 198)
    - Psychological Services, Bureau of 1957-1958 (Box 198)
    - Qualifications for Appointment and Promotion 1954 (Box 198)
    - Report
      - Committee Improvement Writing Skills May, 1961 (Box 198)
      - Distribution Program 1956 (Box 198)
    - Requests to Board of Regents
      - 1922 (Box 198)
      - 1923 (Box 198)
      - 1924 (Box 198)
      - 1925 (Box 198)
      - 1926 (Box 198)
      - 1927 (Box 198)
      - 1928 (Box 198)
      - 1929 (Box 198)
      - 1930 (Box 198)
      - 1931 (Box 198)
      - 1932 (Box 198)
      - 1933 (Box 198)
    - Research--LSA--College Administration August, 1957 (Box 198)
    - Revised Resolution 1963 (Box 198)
    - Revision of Form "C" (Promotions, etc.) 1962-1963 (Box 198)
    - Salary Scales 1963-1965 (Box 198)
    - School Services, Bureau of 1956-1957 (Box 198)
    - Science
      - Engineering Curriculum (Box 198)
      - History of, Course 1956-1957 (Box 198)
      - Teachers Program 1956-1957 (Box 198)
    - Senior Questionnaire 1950, 1956 (Box 198)
    - Social Welfare Research, Coordinating Committee on 1955-1958 (Box 198)
    - Space and Building Needs 1961-1962 (Box 198)
    - Special Committee on Long-Range Policy Planning February, 1964
    - Student
      - Affairs, Office of
        - Report February, 1962 (Box 198)
      - Government 1956-1957 (Box 198)
      - Housing/Social Life November, 1961 (Box 198)
      - Opinion, Committee May 18, 1954 (Box 198)
    - Summer Session 1963 (Box 198)
    - Teacher Training
      - 1957-1959 (Box 198)
      - Evaluation 1957 (Box 198)
    - Teaching Fellows
      - Committee
        - Stipends 1964 (Box 198)
        - Summary of Effective Use 1960-1961 (Box 198)
    - Television February, 1958 (Box 198)
    - Testing Service, Educational 1956-1957 (Box 198)
    - Transfer Students (Box 198)
    - Utilization of College Resources Questionnaires 1956 (Box 198)
    - Admissions 1958 (Box 199)
    - Appointments, Resignations, and Terminations 1955-1958 (Box 199)
    - Budget Analysis 1955-1957 (Box 199)
    - Building and Space Needs 1960-1961 (Box 199)
    - Committee
      - Announcement 1953-1954 (Box 199)
      - Asian Studies 1956-1959 (Box 199)
      - Curriculum 1967-1968 (Box 199)
      - Examination Procedures 1957-1958 (Box 199)
      - Executive
        - Controlling the Size of the College, Report 1/27/1965 (Box 199)
      - Great Books 1956-1958 (Box 199)
      - Natural Science Study 1955-1958 (Box 199)
      - Program in Latin American Studies 1956-1957 (Box 199)
      - Social Science Study 1955-1958 (Box 199)
    - Curtis Telescope March 9, 1965 (Box 199)
    - Examinations July, 1958 (Box 199)
    - Faculty Meeting Correspondence 1937-1944 (Box 199)
    - Junior Research Aid 1958-1959 (Box 199)
    - Leaves of Absence and Part-Time Service 1955 (Box 199)
    - 1922-1971 (Miscellaneous)
      - 1951-1954 (Box 199)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 199)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 199)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 199)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 199)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of 1958
      - Survey and Proposal on Mediterranean Archaeology 1965-1966 (Box 199)
    - Reports on Curriculum, Honors, and Teacher Education 1955-1959 (Box 199)
    - Staff Count 1955-1958 (Box 199)
    - Statistics
      - Promotion 1955-1957 (Box 199)
    - Statistics
      - Salary 1955-1957 (Box 199)
    - Space Utilization Survey 1965-1966 (Box 199)
  - 1968-1973
    - Associate Dean (1968-1970) and Acting Dean (1970-1971) (Box 201)
    - Alfred Sussman Subject Files
      - Afro-American Studies Center 1970-1971 (Box 201)
      - Biological Sciences (Reorganization) 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 201)
      - Environmental Studies Proposed Program 1970-1971 (Box 201)
      - Faculty and Tenure Matters 1968-1970 (Box 201)
      - Graduate Requirements, Commission on 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 201)